Tuesday, June 21, 2022.
We'll have the invocation from the Soppel's Master at First Christmas to Brandon Futter.
What is bound? Father, thank you so much.
First thing you've done for us. We thank you for being creator and sustainer.
We thank you for the responsibility you've given us as stewards of your creation.
God, we love this community. We love my am and we pray that
we will make festive decisions possible for moving forward.
We would stir it in a way to honor you.
So Father, we ask that you bless this meeting.
Bless and give wisdom to everybody involved in making decisions
and help us to make our community a great place to live.
Father, we love you. Make us more like Jesus.
And His name would break. Amen.
Amen.
I'd like to lead us to the five of the United States of America
and to the Republic or the United States.
For our public input or unscheduled personal appearances,
five consent agenda staff recommends we approve out of six and seven.
So, the second.
So, cool.
All right.
Eight.
Number 22, Dastroin 9, MSUA, wastewater collection.
Which is a reimbursable loan.
They're getting, they've spent the money. They're getting it back.
Boom.
The WRB.
And it's a reimbursable loan.
So, they don't start charging as interest and still we act until we actually get the money.
So, title will spend a bunch of money.
And then we tell them, hey, we spend this much money.
We need that back.
All right.
Projects.
Mike, motion to approve.
Sorry.
Parker.
Hi.
Michael.
He's dead.
Hi.
Good night.
Cadale Stratton.
Cleanings for GRDA Realizing Team.
You should have a claim for Larry Bork.
$6,300, $31.57.
We're just consulting services for the realizes.
I'll make a motion to include a second.
So, both, each step, Davis, Summer, and St. Parker.
All right, 10.
The player that proposed items listed in the packet, and surplus and authorized items to be offered
for public sale or sold for high scrap metal value, but authorized their destruction to protect sensitive information.
We're looking at a lot of things to take directly to scrap, or scrap value,
to spell like it's our better return.
I'm really excited about the airplane engine, because I have to read all about this particular aircraft.
And I mean, it's a classic from the 50s, so as a plane, it's no good.
But those engines could draw us in money.
So, can't wait for that one.
So, do you have any questions on any of the surplus items?
Just like the point out that I pointed the airplane engines out to Kevin just now as well.
Just before you said it.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Maybe it.
Those are like holding engines, by the way.
So, I do have the help now.
But I didn't find those engines.
H.T. and play out about, like I need to say, that they're awesome.
How do they come out of?
Awesome work.
What do they come out of?
And then you know what I'm pointing out?
This is the point that it was just a band of airport in order to somewhere.
It was right here to kind of ran.
We went through the process.
Some letters.
One file.
Two files.
A band.
He was going to try to take a part all out.
And he stripped a bunch.
All the interior.
All the melodies.
Like in between the wings of the fuselage.
I can turn them out.
So, some parts.
They can never be put back together.
Well, it's probably made of it.
The engines are there.
The cores.
Because it's been sitting for so long.
It's probably said 50-20 years.
Never find it.
This is cores.
They were.
One hundred hour engines.
And good operating conditions.
About twenty dollars.
Wow.
Core.
Get them out of line.
But no 320.
And it's great in this.
So, we have to rebuild them here.
And in the rest of the work, I know, the person's blown out of it.
That's all I can do.
Send me because the baby is so beautiful.
In the 1950s classic that's highly sought after,
if it were in good condition, we would have a great, we'd have it, we'd have it, you know.
So, and just an update we closed our most recent auction on Monday
and we actually brought in $11,000 to $50,000.
However, we're going with the biggest piece of that was for a great all.
We didn't quite reach what we could get on the actual trade-in values
and we'll probably get a decline method and trade it in.
I'm talking with the deals now about that.
Did you find the dragon tablet?
I mean, I didn't see it on the list, that's why I asked.
You know, because I'm looking at it.
I think it's an ancient, because they were 10 years old.
I don't know.
I mean, I didn't see it on the list, that's why I asked.
You know, because I'm looking at it.
I think it's an ancient because they were 10 years old.
I think it might be there.
You thought this was going to be boring.
Leave it to Brian.
So, the main street called the Chop Door is that one of the old doors?
It's not an original door.
I pretty certain it sounds original door, but it is not a new door.
And I can't even tell you where it came from.
I thought it first.
It was colleagues.
But what I saw.
It's not over.
It was large door.
Any other questions?
I just want to remind you that the reason we use gut deals as opposed to hiring a local or any option here is the cost.
We get every bit of the bit.
Money.
And gut deals takes care of getting all the taxes.
All of there.
You know, they get their percentage from mark up and everything.
Another it comes up.
So they use a virus premium to cover themselves.
Yes, that's right.
Okay.
Most of them.
There you go.
Davis.
All right.
Senberg.
Don't call.
Hi.
Each step.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr.
11.
Any new business?
There's a reason since posting of this agenda.
12 staff reports.
13 trustee community announcements.
14 adjournments.
Okay.
Bye.